Here, we have an object called cat as well as a function, sayHello.
这里有一个叫做 cat 的对象以及一个叫做 sayHello 的函数
All sayHello does is taking a single parameter and prints out a message to the console.
sayHello 的作用是传入单个参数并向控制台中输出一条消息
Now, this might look kind of peculiar,
看起来可能有点奇怪
because sayHello actually references the "this" keyword.
因为 sayHello 实际上引用的是关键字
If we invoked sayHello as a function,
如果我们将 sayHello 当做函数来调用它
what would "this" get set to?
this 会设成什么？
Well, it would get set to window or the global object.
它会设成一个窗口或全局对象
So, if you wanted "this" to refer to cat,
如果你希望 this 引用的是 cat
we can do it ourselves manually using the special call or apply methods.
我们可以使用特殊的 call 或 apply 方法手动地进行设置
Let's check out how we can do that, starting with call.
我们看看如何设置 先从 call 开始
Call's a method that we can invoke directly onto a function. Let's go ahead and do that.
call 是可以直接在函数中调用的方法 我们来调用它
We can pass in two arguments right now into the call method.
现在可以向 call 方法中传入两个参数
First, it'll be the object that we bind "this" to which will be cat.
首先 是 this 绑定到的对象 即 cat
Next, it's a set of arguments passed into the function that call is being called on,
接着 是向调用 call 所在的函数传入的一组参数
in this case would be Hello,
这里是 sayHello 函数
and we know that it takes in a single argument. Just message.
我们知道它有一个参数 即一条消息
Let's go ahead and pass on that message.
传入该消息
Great, let's go ahead and execute this and see what we get.
运行代码 看看结果如何
And there you have it. Nice to see you, Bailey.
消息显示出来了 Nice to see you, Bailey
We can actually achieve the same results using the apply method,
我们可以使用 apply 方法获得相同的结果
but the arguments passed on are a little bit different.
但是传入的参数稍微不同
Let's check it out. I'll switch to
我们来看看
the other window right now to give myself a little bit more space here.
我将切换到另一个窗口中 以便有更多的空间
Just like call, apply is directly invoked onto a function.
和 call 一样 apply 会直接在函数中调用
The first argument should be the same,
第一个参数一样
which is just the object that you want to bind this to, in this case would be cat.
即要绑定到的对象 这里是 cat
Next, rather than separating individual arguments that will be passed
接着 不再是用逗号分隔将传入 sayHello 函数中的参数
into the sayHello function by commas like we do with call,
就像 call 一样
apply actually takes in all the arguments in the form of an array.
apply 像数组一样接收所有的参数
Again, we know in this case it's a single argument
这里是一个参数
because sayHello only takes in message.
因为 sayHello 只接收一个消息
So let's go ahead and pass on our message in an array.
我们以数组的形式传入消息
Great, let's invoke it and see what happens.
调用它 看看结果怎样
Hello, Bailey. There we go.
Hello, Bailey 就是这个结果
Call and apply are great ways to set the value of "this" ourselves.
Call 和 apply 是手动设置 this 值的很好方式